Bardsley, William Collection of United States National Recovery Administrations and National War Labor Board Printed and Mimeographed Documents 5699
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
William Bardsley Collection of United States National Recovery Administrations and National War Labor Board Printed and Mimeographed Documents
1933-1945
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Bardsley, William
National Recovery Administrations (NRA)
National War Labor Board (NWLB)
5699
8 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3122541
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 03, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 27, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5391: U.S. National Recovery Administration Printed Documents from the Division Review
Bardsley, William W.,; United States. National Recovery Administration--Sources.; United States. National War Labor Board (1918-1919)--Sources.
3122541
- A-C (Box 1)
  - Actions of the National Industrial Recovery Board (Sept. 28, 1934-May 27, 1935) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Actions of the National Industrial Recovery Board Part 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Orders (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The NRA Policy Group Vol 1 (A to D Inclusive) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The NRA Policy Group Vol. II (E to P Inclusive) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The NRA Policy Group Vol. III (R to Y Inclusive) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Compendium of Policy Abstracts (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Statement of Policy - NRA (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Executive Order: Creating a Committee to Complete the Summary of the Results and Accomplishments of the National Recovery Administration and Report Thereon (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Development and Application of NRA Policies as to the Provisions of the Codes (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Organization, Procedures and Administrative Problems of the National Recovery Administration (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - National Recovery Administration Division of Research and Planning - Gertrude Working (11/20/1934) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - General NRA Information (Box 1, Folder 13)
- D1-D29 (Box 2)
  - National Recovery Administration Division of Review - Work Materials #1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - National Recovery Administration Division of Review - Work Materials #2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #3 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Review #4 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #5 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #6 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #7 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #8 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #9 Vol. 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #9 Vol. 2 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #9 Vol. 3 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #11 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #12 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #13 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #15 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #16 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #19 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - NRA Division o f Review - Work Materials #17 Part A-C (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #17 Part D-F (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #20-21 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #22-23 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #24 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #25 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #26-27 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #28 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #29 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- D30-D44 (Box 3)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #30 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #31 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #32 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #33 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #34 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #35NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #35 (1 of 4) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #35 (2 of 4) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #35 (3 of 4) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #35 (4 of 4) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #36 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #37 Vol. 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #37 Vol. 2 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #38 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #40 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #39 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #40 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #41 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #42 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #43 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #44 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- D45-D59 (Box 4)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #45 Part A (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #45 Part B (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials No. 45 Pt. C (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #45 Pt C (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #45 Pt D (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #45 Pt D (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #45 Pt D (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Material #45 Pt E (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #46 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #47 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #48 and 49 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #50 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #51 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #52 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #53 and 54 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #55 and 56 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #57 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #58 and 59 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- D60-D75 (Box 5)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #60 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #61 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #62 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #63 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #64 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #65 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #66-68 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #69 Vol. 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #69 Vol. 2 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #70 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #71 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #72 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #73 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #74 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NRA Division of Review - Work Materials #75 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- D76-D86 (Box 6)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #80 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #80 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #82 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #83 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #84 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #85 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #86 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - The Tobacco Study (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #76 Vol. 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #76 Vol. 2 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #77 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #78 Vol. 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Office of the National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #78 Vol. 2 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Work Materials #79 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- D/E - E 1 of 3 (Box 7)
  - National Recovery Administration: Report on the Aluminum Industry and the Preliminary Report on Automobile Industry (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - National Recovery Administration: Preliminary Report in the Automobile Industry - Appendix A and B (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - National Recovery Administration: Automobile Industry - Appendix C (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Office of National Recovery Administration - Division of Review - Statistical Materials #128 and 410 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Report of National Recovery Administration: Iron and Steel Industry (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Iron and Steel Industry Report: Appendix A-D (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Iron and Steel Report: Appendix E (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - NRA Code: Report on Wholesale and Retail Changes Between 1929 and 1933 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - US Department of Commerce - Retail Distribution (1933) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial Number 30E and 31 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #33 and 34 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #35-37 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #39-42 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #45 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #48-50 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #52-55 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #57, 58, 61, and 62 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #64, 67-70 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #71-74 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #76-79, 82-86 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #88-93 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #95-101 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #103-109 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #110-115 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #117-123 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - Serial #126-130 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- E 2 and 3 of 3 and miscellaneous and books (Box 8)
  - NRA Research and Planning Division - 1/30-2/2/1935 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - NRA Code - Prices and Price Provisions in Codes (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - NRA Code: Hours, Wages and Employment Under the Codes (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - NRA Code: Tabulation of Labor Provisions in Codes Approved by August 8, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - NRA Code: Geographic and Population Differentials in Minimum Wages (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - NRA Code: Report on the Operation of NIRA (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - NRA Code: Charts on the Operation of NIRA (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - NRA Code: Tables on the Operation of NIRA (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - NIRA Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - NRA Poster (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - NRA Articles (1935) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Minutes of Meetings of Third Regional Labor Supply Committee (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Hours and Wages Provisions in NRA Codes - by Leon c. Marshall (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - The National Recovery Administration: An Analysis and an Appraisal (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - National Recovery Administration: Codes of Fair Competition No. 1-57 Vol. ! (6/14-10/11/1933) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - The Problem of Abuse in Unemployment Benefits (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - The Rainbow - Donald R. Richberg (Box 8, Folder 17)